togo-download.com 2018-12-27

# togo-download.com - The latest software for free

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy regulates important questions concerning the privacy of the users of this website. The Company protects and guarantees security in the collection and processing of the data that is affected through this website as well as the compliance with the current policy with regards to data protection. The following paragraphs inform about the Company’s procedures of data collection and processing.

**1\. Data Collection**

The Company shall collect and process the data that users enter on the forms available on this website, or which are communicated to the Company by any other means. When a user visits the website, the Company shall collect tracking information like IP address, browser and operative system, details about computer hardware, applications already installed on the PC, and pages visited on the website. None of this information is to identify the user personally.

The Data can consist of users personal details, in accordance with the definition given for this concept by current European law and, on providing them in the forms, or in the automatically captured Data, on browsing this website, users shall be revealing their consent to the collection of same, their entry onto a file and their processing by the Company in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The user hereby states and guarantees that he or she shall not provide personal data that refer to third parties, even with the consent of the latter, and shall assume any liability before the Company that such conduct may give rise to.

**2\. Purpose of data processing**

The Company shall process the Data for the purpose of maintenance, development and control of the website and services provided mainly in order to respond and solve errors reported by users about the services provided.

Moreover, under the user explicit authorization, the Company can use the Data to send business messages, even via electronic means, in order to promote the Company’s goods and services, or those of a third party. The authorisation provided by users can be withdrawn at any time.

Regarding the purposes stated above, the user authorises the Company to process the Data outside the European Union, particularly in the United States of America, either personally or by means of commissioning the processing operation, even in spite of the fact that the legislation of the country where the data are to be processed does not provide personal data with the same level of protection as provided by the European law.

The Data shall not be used for purposes other than those set forth in this Privacy Policy, nor shall be transferred to third parties without the user’s prior consent.

**3\. Cookies**

This website uses cookies in order to enable the Company to provide a better service to the user, including interest-based advertising. Users can configure their internet browser to alert them to the reception of cookies, thus affording them the possibility of deciding whether to accept the cookies in question or not.

**4\. Right to access, rectification, cancellation and objection**

Users can exercise their rights to access, rectification, cancellation and objection as stated by the European law regarding personal data protection. The data holders may communicate their intentions by sending an email to: support@freeware4win.com

**5\. Other websites**

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to this website. The Company neither guarantees nor accepts any liability for the privacy policies that apply to the websites that are linked from this website, or the data processing that may be carried out by those responsible for aforementioned websites.
